<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.eeat.knime.connector.feature"
      label="EEAT KNIME connectors"
      version="3.0.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="wrobinson.cis.gsu.edu">

   <description url="http://wrobinson.cis.gsu.edu/reqmon">
      EEAT KNIME Google connector nodes, and Git connector nodes.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.example.com/copyright">
      * Copyright (c) 2005-2009
*      William N. Robinson  All rights reserved.
*
* Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or
without
* modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
* are met:
* 1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
*    notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
* 2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above
copyright
*    notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
in the
*    documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
* 3. All advertising materials mentioning features or use of
this software
*    must display the following acknowledgment:
*      This product includes software developed by the William
N. Robinson
*      and its contributors.
* 4. Neither the name of William N. Robinson nor the names of
its contributors
*    may be used to endorse or promote products derived from
this software
*    without specific prior written permission.
*
* THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY William N. Robinson AND CONTRIBUTORS
``AS IS&apos;&apos; AND
* ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED
TO, THE
* IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
PURPOSE
* ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL William N. Robinson OR CONTRIBUTORS
BE LIABLE
* FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
CONSEQUENTIAL
* DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE
GOODS
* OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
* HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT,
STRICT
* LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING
IN ANY WAY
* OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY
OF
* SUCH DAMAGE.
e.]
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.example.com/license">
      * Copyright (c) 2005-2009
*      William N. Robinson  All rights reserved.
*
* Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
* modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
* are met:
* 1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
*    notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
* 2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
*    notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
*    documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
* 3. All advertising materials mentioning features or use of this software
*    must display the following acknowledgment:
*      This product includes software developed by the William N. Robinson
*      and its contributors.
* 4. Neither the name of William N. Robinson nor the names of its contributors
*    may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software
*    without specific prior written permission.
*
* THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY William N. Robinson AND CONTRIBUTORS ``AS IS&apos;&apos; AND
* ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
* IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
* ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL William N. Robinson OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE
* FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
* DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS
* OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
* HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT
* LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY
* OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF
* SUCH DAMAGE.
[Enter License Description here.]
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="EEAT update site" url="http://eeat.cis.gsu.edu:9080/update"/>
      <discovery label="EEAT update site" url="http://eeat.cis.gsu.edu:9080/update"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime" version="3.7.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.knime.workbench.core" version="2.8.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.knime.workbench.repository" version="2.8.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.knime.base" version="2.8.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.eeat.knime.google.bigquery.node"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eeat.knime.git.commentprinter"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eeat.knime.git.issuecommentprinter"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eeat.knime.git.prcommentprinter"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eeat.knime.git.prprinter"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eeat.knime.git.issueprinter"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eeat.knime.mongo.node"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
